Contact

Buru-un, Iligan City, Lanao del Norte, Philippines +639556789804 (Mobile) ehlacastillon@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ehla-castillon (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL

Discuss Oracle Cloud Data Management Principles Explain Oracle Free Tier Accounts

Certifications

Certified Virtual Sales and Admin Assistant

Getting Grounded on Analytics SQL for Business Users

Python Programming Essentials Course Certificate of Completion 2023

Oracle Cloud Data Management 2023 Certified Foundations Associate

Ehla Castillon

--

Iligan, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

Summary

An experienced front desk Filipina receptionist who is part of a customer service role with a demonstrated history of performing administrative tasks and warming the hearts of clients in the business industry. A part-time English Second Language teacher now, who teaches for communication to bring connections and understanding internationally. And a skilled one who has experience in the technological industry as a computer system service and support assistant to the main technician, molded much of the computer literacy of the said industry. Aside from that, a person with background knowledge of programming, particularly frontend development, and with a backbone programming language of cascading style sheets (CSS), C++, HTML, and Java, learned it all from one of the prestigious universities in the Philippines.

Experience

Fabrigar Virtual Assistant April 2021 - June 2022 (1 year 3 months) United States

51Talk

English Second Language Teacher February 2021 - June 2022 (1 year 5 months)

Own a Small Business
Fine Artist
August 2016 - December 2020 (4 years 5 months)
Iligan, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

IPLAY CyberSquare
Front Desk Receptionist
January 2018 - December 2019 (2 years)
Iligan, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

AdTech Computer Sales and Services 2 months

Computer Support Technician November 2017 - December 2017 (2 months) Iligan, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

Computer Service Technician November 2017 - December 2017 (2 months) Iligan, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

Computer System Technician November 2017 - December 2017 (2 months) Iligan, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

Education

Mindanao State University- Naawan

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (January 2019 - January 2024)

IHelp Coaching and Business Solutions Incorporated

Certified Virtual Sales and Admin Assistant (August 2021 - September 2021)

Mindanao State University-Iligan Institute of Technology
Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Application · (August 2018 - January 2019)

La Salle Academy

Technical Vocational in Computer System Servicing · (June 2016 - March 2018)

HarvardX

CS50 Web Programming with Python and JavaScript · (October 2021)